



j.r.h.wood98@gmail.com





Third-year engineering student majoring in Software. Finding an opportunity to apply and expand my knowledge. Highly motivated and ready to learn new things, with experience in the service industry and a passion for all things tech.



Keras Tensorflow Sklearn Jupy

Jupyter χ

Weka

Kaggle













### **EXPERIENCE**

2020 - Now part time

## Software Developer Internship

Niwa

My work experience involved developing a geographic information system (GIS). This used the Mapserver framework to create a web map service (WMS) to render data stored on a PostGIS database.

postgres / mapserver / linux

2018 - 2019

## Bartender, Barista, Mixologist, Maitre D'

St. Johns Bar and Eatery

I furthered my communication skills from serving the upmarket clientele. This included supervising functions for Ministers of Parliament and their cabinets. We regularly hosted the staff for Xero and TradeMe.

conflict resolution / health and safety / customer service

2012 - 2018

#### Bartender, Barista, Kitchenhand

Mac's Brewery

This was my first job. I started with no work experience and steadily progressed through the company. I learnt valuable communication, event coordination and conflict resolution skills. time management / communication

**EDUCATION** 

2016 - Now

# **Batchelor of Engineering (Hons)**

Victoria University of Wellington

Victoria Excellence Scholarship

Machine Learning, Mobile Software, Group Project, Game Dev

2011 - 2015

#### NCEA Level 3 endorsed with Excellence

Rongotai

Scholarship English, Schools Canoe Polo

Prefect, UN Youth Ambassador, Debating, Rockquest, Jazz Band, Production Band

**PROJECTS** 

**Data Ingestion** 

Python / Postgres /

GeoServer
Map Service

Postgres / MapServer /

Apache

MCS

React.js / Mapserver /
Leaflet

HOBBIES

Sciences

CS, AI, Robotics, Astrophysics,

Psychology

Guitar

Classical, Jazz, Blues, Classic Rock

Sports

Canoe Polo, Table Tennis, Indoor

Football

REFERENCES

Andrea Mari - Niwa

E: · Andea.Mari@niwa.co.nz

P: · 022434 2053

Tom Moorhead - Mac's

E: · tom@sscateriing.co.nz

P: · 0211395980

Troy Savage - Mac's

E: · tsavage.nz@gmaill.com

**P:** · 0220657129